antennaweb.org 2017-12-16

# Privacy Policy

At **TitanTV, Inc** , we recognize the importance of privacy to users of AntennaWeb.org. This Privacy Policy explains what type of information may be collected from you when you access AntennaWeb.org and how that information may be used. Please note that this Privacy Policy pertains only to AntennaWeb.org, and is separate and distinct from the privacy policies, end user license agreements, terms or service, or terms of use governing: (a) YouNews®; (b) the web sites, applications and services of TITANTV's clients; (c) the web sites, applications and services that may link to or from AntennaWeb.org; and (d) other TITANTV web sites, applications or services. 

Gathering of Information

TITANTV may collect personally-identifying information from AntennaWeb.org for a variety of purposes. Such personally identifying information may include, but is not limited to, your address. 

TITANTV may ask you to provide certain personal information when you register for certain features or services that TITANTV may include AntennaWeb.org. TITANTV also may ask you to provide personal information in other limited circumstances specified at the time the information is gathered. Any information that you submit on or through AntennaWeb.org may become public. 

Like all other Web servers, TITANTV's Web server may automatically create log files for each user who accesses AntennaWeb.org. These "access logs" may allow TITANTV to make AntennaWeb.org more useful to our users. The access logs may record the identifier provided for your mobile device by your wireless carrier ("carrier identifier"). Otherwise, the access logs do NOT record a user's name, address, e-mail address, credit card numbers, or any other personally-identifying information. Rather, they may contain some or all of the following information:

  * The Internet Protocol Address (IP Address) of the device which downloaded, installed or used the Mobile Application. 
  * The date of use.
  * The time of use.
  * The path taken through AntennaWeb.org.
  * The operating system and device type being used.
  * A list of files downloaded or viewed.
  * The amount of time spent listening to/viewing media files.
  * Any errors encountered.
  * The device’s geographic location.

Cookies and Other Technologies

TITANTV may also use 'cookies' to collect information. A cookie is a string of characters that can be written to a file on the user's device when the user accesses AntennaWeb.org. 

TITANTV may use cookies to track users' activity through AntennaWeb.org in order to improve the site, the application architecture, to offer the features that would not be possible without them, to offer third party content, and to recall specific information to save the user time during subsequent use of AntennaWeb.org. For example, cookies may allow TITANTV to remember your (and/or your device’s) location. Interactive features may also use cookies. Our sponsorship service vendors, which serve sponsorship messages onto AntennaWeb.org, and third party vendors that measure and analyze the use of AntennaWeb.org for TITANTV, may also use their own cookies. 

TITANTV and the third party vendors that measure and analyze use of AntennaWeb.org for TITANTV also may use web beacons, alone or in conjunction with cookies, to help compile information about and facilitate usage of AntennaWeb.org. A web beacon is an electronic image, also known as a single-pixel (1x1) or clear .gif., which can be used to recognize certain information on your device, such as cookies, the time and date of your actions within AntennaWeb.org, and a description of where content is placed. We may use web beacons on AntennaWeb.org from time to time for this and other purposes. 

Use of Information

TITANTV may use personally-identifying information to: 

  * manage or administer AntennaWeb.org;
  * optimize or customize the delivery of advertising or content to you and other users of AntennaWeb.org; 
  * respond to user messages; 
  * list device location (city, state and/or country) information;
  * contact users for an online survey;
  * send e-mail newsletters and other communications, including marketing and promotional communications, from TITANTV, TITANTV sponsors, TITANTV suppliers, TITANTV licensors, and TITANTV clients to users; 
  * other internal TITANTV or TITANTV client purposes; and/or
  * for other purposes specified at the time the information is gathered.

Excluding information provided by the user, which may become public as discussed above, personally-identifying information collected by TITANTV may be given to the following third parties: 

  * TITANTV’s clients, suppliers, licensors, advertising partners, and service vendors; and 
  * other third parties when you specifically consent to such distribution (such as the disclosure of your name to a friend when you email, send via SMS or text message, or otherwise share a story to that friend). 

In these circumstances, the information is provided to a third party for the purposes of 

  * send e-mail newsletters and other communications, including marketing and promotional communications, from TITANTV, TITANTV sponsors, TITANTV suppliers, TITANTV licensors, and TITANTV clients to users; 
  * delivering communications from TITANTV or TITANTV clients, suppliers, licensors, advertising partners or service vendors; 
  * providing services for and on behalf of TITANTV; or 
  * serving other TITANTV purposes.

TITANTV also may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or if it believes that such action is necessary to: (a) comply with the law or with legal process, (b) protect against misuse or unauthorized use of AntennaWeb.org, or (c) protect the personal safety or property of users of AntennaWeb.org, the public or TITANTV and its employees. 

If you do not want your personally-identifying information to be collected or used for any of these purposes, please do not provide it and do not access AntennaWeb.org. 

Third-Party Advertising

We use several third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you access AntennaWeb.org. Some of these companies may use information about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements on AntennaWeb.org and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by some of these companies, please [click here.](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)

Security

TITANTV has in place what we believe to be appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. However, no Internet, e-mail or mobile transmission is ever fully secure or error free and TITANTV cannot guarantee that any information will be or remain safe or secure. Because most e-mail and mobile transmissions are not encrypted, you should take special care in deciding what information you send to us via e-mail, SMS or text message, or other mobile transmission. 

Children

If you are under 13 years of age, please do not access AntennaWeb.org. AntennaWeb.org is not intended for children under 13, and TITANTV will not knowingly collect any information from any children under the age of 13. If we discover that we have collected any personally-identifying information from a child under the age of 13, we will promptly remove that information from our database. 

Acceptance of Privacy Policy Terms

TITANTV reserves the right to change this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted to this page as soon as reasonably possible, so please check this page periodically. Use of AntennaWeb.org constitutes consent to any policy then in effect. 

Links to other Sites and Services

It is important to note that AntennaWeb.org may contain links to other sites, applications and services maintained by third parties that may not follow the same privacy policies as AntennaWeb.org. For instance, clicking or tapping on a sponsorship notice or some third party logos on AntennaWeb.org will take you to an entirely different site, application or service. These sites, applications and services may use cookies, collect data, and use the data in ways that AntennaWeb.org would not. TITANTV is not responsible for the privacy practices or any information or materials on these other sites, applications and services. Please visit these sites or applications if you wish to review their privacy policies. 

AntennaWeb.org may in the future include certain embedded tools provided and controlled by third parties and governed by the terms and policies of the third parties. You should only use these third party tools if you agree to their respective terms and policies. 

AntennaWeb.org may include a tool that allows you to sign in using information from your account with a third party service, such as Facebook, Twitter, Google, Yahoo, OpenID, or LinkedIn. Please be aware that those third party services are unrelated to TITANTV, and that your use of the third party services is subject to the terms and policies of those services. 

International User Notice

For international users, please note that it may be necessary to transfer your information internationally and, in particular, your information may be transferred to and processed in the United States. For residents of the European Union: the data protection and other laws of other countries outside of the European Union may not be as comprehensive as those of the European Union. Please be assured that we take steps to ensure that your privacy is protected as described in this policy. By accessing AntennaWeb.org, you agree to have your information used and transferred to the United States as set forth in this policy. If you access AntennaWeb.org from the European Union, Asia, or any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use and disclosure that differ from United States laws, please be advised that through your continued use of AntennaWeb.org, which is governed by U.S. law and this Privacy Policy, you are transferring your personal information to the United States and you consent to that transfer. 

In the Event of Merger, Sale, or Bankruptcy

In the event that TITANTV or AntennaWeb.org business is acquired by or merged with a third party entity, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information we have collected from our users as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control. In the unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors' rights generally, we may not be able to control how your personal information is treated, transferred, or used. 

Questions

If you have any questions or comments concerning our Privacy Policy, please contact us at [legal@titantv.com](mailto:legal@titantv.com?subject=Antenna%20Web%20Privacy%20Policy%20Feedback "Click here to email TITANTV regarding this Privacy Policy."). 

Last Updated: May 23, 2012
